#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ngan-nguyen-b82064a1 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Customer Service Management

### Languages

English (Professional Working)
Spanish (Elementary)

### Certifications

Shane Snow on Storytelling
The Neuroscience of Emotional
Intelligence and Self-Awareness
Employee Experience
HR as a Business Partner
Duolingo Spanish Fluency: Beginner
(Estimated)

# Ngan Nguyen

HR & Talent Acquisition Lead
Da Nang Metropolitan Area

## Summary

A passionate Human Resources & Talent Acquisition Lead with more than 9 years of experience in international working environments and Technology Industry. I'm versatile, interested in psychology, excellent at interpersonal skills and proficient in English.

I'm always striving to expand my horizon & open for new connections. Reach me at hongngan36k17@gmail.com or Skype: ngannguyen2309.

## Experience

IPS AG HR & Talent Acquisition Lead July 2021 - Present (3 years 9 months) Da Nang City, Vietnam

IPS is a German-owned high-tech company with development centres in the Czech Republic and in Vietnam with focus on Microsoft technologies as a Microsoft Gold Partner. IPS offers a unique opportunity for developers to join our experienced teams and work on large-scale long term international projects.

Sioux High Tech Software Ltd.
6 years 4 months
Senior Human Resources Executive
February 2017 - January 2021 (4 years)
Vietnam

Sioux High Tech Software, whose parent company is based in The Netherlands, established in Vietnam in 2012.

Human Resources Executive
October 2014 - October 2017 (3 years 1 month)
6th Floor - Petrolimex Building, 122 2/9 Street, Danang

The Fred Hollows Foundation

## Human Resources Intern

April 2014 - October 2014 (7 months)

7th Floor - Sacombank Tower, 130 Bach Dang, Danang

The Fred Hollows Foundation is a non-profit aid organization based in Australia founded in 1992 by eye surgeon Fred Hollows. The Foundation focuses on treating and preventing blindness and other vision problems. It operates in Australia, The Pacific, South and South East Asia, and Africa.

## Education

Da Nang University Of Economics
Bachelor's degree, Human Resource Management